(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Penny:)And this is also
not the right time.
(Penny:)Do not propose.
(Penny:)-What?
-I know that face.
(Penny:)That's your propose face.
(Leonard:)I was not gonna propose.
it's already two to one.
(Penny:)What's two to one?
(Leonard:)I proposed twice,
you proposed once. Two to one.
(Penny:)Oh, my... It's not a contest.
(Leonard:)I don't know what
you're upset about.
(Leonard:)-I'm the one who's losing.
-OK.
(Penny:)Fine. Would you feel
better it I propose
so you could tum
me down again?
(Leonard:)Yeah, I think I would.
OK. Leonard,
will you marry me?
(Sheldon:)Hm...
(Penny:)No, don't you dare.
(Penny:)You reject me right
now and tie things up.
(Leonard:)It's just such a big decision.
(Leonard:)I don't want to have any regrets.
(Amy:)Did you ever watch Professor Proton
when you were a kid?
(Bernadette:)No. My dad controlled the TV,
(Bernadette:)So unless someone
was a Texas Ranger,
(Bernadette:)Jake or the Fatman,
we didn't see it.
(Amy:)I never watched him, either,
but he seems to be the reason
(Amy:)that Sheldon got interested
in science.
(Bernadette:)Not me. I got into science